we are in week six of making history I'm
going to be turning one of these hundred
dollars into a million dollars right I
can't believe that we're already a month
and a half into this challenge
absolutely everything is going to be
documented here on my YouTube Instagram
telegram Discord so you guys can follow
along every single one of my trades you
guys can see them before the during the
after and learn from my mistakes we
started five weeks ago where I took my
first attempt at it and I blew the
account we started from zero and then I
turned a hundred dollars into then 155
when the 155 to about two thousand two
thousand four thousand four thousand to
seven thousand seven thousand to
nineteen thousand and then now we're
gonna be trying turning these nineteen
thousand dollars to forty thousand
dollars I can already feel me completing
this challenge so let's get started with
the video so you guys see what
everything is about
[Music]
all right so it is Sunday it is
officially
the challenge for this week you guys
already know
we're gonna be hitting the 40K mark this
week we're going to be turning the
hundred dollars into the mail so if you
guys didn't see last week's series make
sure you guys check it out we just
finished doing Sunday Swings with the
students now let's break down my top
three trades for the week so let's get
into it so the first trade is going to
be GBP cash so if you guys can tell GDP
guy last week we were literally the
first trade that we caught was at the
beginning I mean it was at the end of
the week where we then caught this
rejection from the area of interest to
shift the structure head to the upside
and we closed right before the pullback
of the whole entire market so my
prediction from this week it is
extremely simple all three time frames
all two time frames are bullish except
the four hour where it is currently
bearish but that's fine because it's
being outweighed by the weekly and the
daily time frame so this is going to
give us a base of a 20 Confluence
towards my grade of the trade what I do
like is how we are rejecting this very
strong daily area of Interest we have
one top two top three top daily doji
rejection from area of interest and then
now the one hour is coming back to
retest this area and and potentially
create an inverted head and shoulders I
had this alarm earlier this morning I
mean earlier this afternoon when I was
doing the Sunday Swings with the
students price hit it perfectly now I
have my alarm right around here because
I'm going to be waiting for price to
give me any little pull back to enter
this trade to then head to the upside I
will be having my first take profit area
right around this level and then my
second take profit area right around
this level right here I will only be
interested in buying GBP CAD next is
Euro JPY so this is kind of like a
little bit of a ballsy trade idea
because we are needing a huge bearish
engulfing Candlestick to then break out
of this structure after it breaks then
pull back re-test area of interest and
then we head to the downside and then
third we have GBP USD which is going to
be a little bit of a longer wait but we
have to wait for price to come back all
the way to this area of Interest which
is the alarm which is also around
psychological level 27 000. so once
price comes back into this level right
here we're then going to have a
rejection from this level so then head
to the downside so those are the top
three pairs for the week as of right now
tomorrow in the morning we're gonna have
the yacht with the Traders where we're
gonna obviously be trading on the yacht
if any trades present themselves so
these are traders that I've literally
flown out from all around the world
Germany Cali some even came from
Argentina there's students of mine from
swing trading lab and they've had over
five figures results a month and then
obviously due to those results I'm like
yo come to Miami on me and um tomorrow
we're gonna see if we can trade on the
yacht and catch any of these trades so
let's see all right so it's currently
nine in the morning so following up from
last night's analysis we have GBP CAD
which if we continue going that we're
going this can be very very valuable uh
currency pair for our success in this
week's trade so let me show you guys
right now how the market is so we are
currently up about two thousand dollars
on GDP CAD with the buys I explained
yesterday which I'm going to explain to
you guys right now exactly what happened
where I entered and where I expect the
price to go so right now GDP CAD if you
guys remember yesterday we were around
this oh this is a trade that we took
last week then I anticipate a pullback
into this level last night we were at
this level right here and then you
notice how I said all right cool in
order for me to take this trade I
actually need to have the pool back into
the area of interest for me to take the
trade so I pretty much took the trade
after this impulse on the 15 minute
which was a beautiful then higher low to
then continue creating higher highs on
the lower time frame I personally love
how this four hour Candlestick is closed
tomorrow busu Candlestick rejection from
the area of Interest after but uh
breaking above this structure point
right here so as of right now I have my
first take profit at this structure
point right here because I feel like
whenever price comes to this area and we
are under we're selling whenever we're
above we're buying whenever we are under
we are uh then selling whenever we are
above we are then buying so as of right
now as of this trade I want to get out
at this area right here first if we do
manage to break above then I'll continue
to hold to this area right here but I'm
going to try and buy and get into more
position on this way up Euro JPY
we are currently pulling up to our area
of Interest where we might be looking to
then reject from we're having some very
clean double doji rejecting candlesticks
but the only way I will take this trade
is if I've been body closed under this
area break and then retest so as of
right now we still haven't gotten that
and then GBP USD we're waiting for this
trade to make it all the way back up
into here so then in order for us to
then sell Euro USD we're just waiting
for it to make it to this alarm area to
then sell so right now the only trade
we're coming in is GBP cache so this is
how we're currently looking on the
account about 1700 in profit good start
to the week you guys saw last week's
series how I only took two trades and
both of them were on Thursday and Friday
and I managed to make all of the profits
for the week on the last two days of the
week so the fact that we got this at the
beginning of the week
all right so stop plus got hit but it's
the way how the stop blast got hit that
annoys me and like I said it before
there's nothing you can do to avoid this
kind of stuff so let me show you guys so
currently we are in the account of
Thirteen thousand dollars so we've lost
about seven thousand dollars this
morning alone to knowing and this is
what pisses me off about it so let me
show you guys so as you guys can see
right here this is the GDP Kai trade
we're anticipating for it yesterday to
pull back into this area we had a
beautiful push and then we've come all
the way back in Wake this out and look
at that where we are now we are now
waking back up to the upside so we
literally if this does not continue to
head to the downside and it rejects from
here and then it does this I'm gonna be
pissed off because it's just crazy how
it just Taps my stop loss and just heads
up to the upside you guys can see here
how in the p l today we just lost a loan
32 of the account because I told you
guys I risked 33 of the account per
trade which is six thousand four hundred
dollars you can see it right here the
piano jar has taken a humongous dip and
it's annoying because we were up
literally 19 800 and now this trade
right here has just Wicked this out and
it's done this so
happens and if that's not enough
something fell out of the sky literally
we're good what are they doing
what are they doing yeah a turtle fell
out of the sky and landed in my backyard
I don't know what to do with it
I don't know what's uh what a name it's
definitely real supposedly this is a
good luck thing it brings wealth it
brings money it brings health
clearly it's not working
so I don't know what to do with this I
don't know if to keep it I'm gonna see
if the cat likes it but I have a cat I
have a goat and now I have a turtle
all right so we just got the Sprinter
right now we got Jordan the first
student the OG students we're gonna pick
up right now the rest of the students
we're gonna head to the yacht weather's
not looking that great it's kind of
Miami weather it is what it is it's part
of the process but we're gonna put it to
the yacht we're gonna go out have some
fun get the jet ski and then kind of
like afternoon late night we're gonna
then do the podcast on the 100 foot
yacht with every single student because
they all have a different success so
whatever you guys are gonna have to go
with Jordan in the back of the jet ski
so who wants to go behind Jordan hey I'm
gonna I'm gonna end up tipping that
thing over if I go buying them
no I should have you seen it I've yes
I've seen it
it's just bigger than I thought that's
your boat
Harbor
[Music]
nothing like being on a yacht at 2 15 on
a Monday right definitely trading
lifestyle
[Music]
in the sketchy stairs I've ever been in
my life so we just got home from the
yacht day it's midnight so we've
literally been out on the yaw all day I
had a beautiful day with the students it
was a beautiful day in Miami had some
crazy conversations on the podcast
Jordan told his story which honestly got
everybody on the boat that was watching
the podcast live emotional including
myself at the whole box in tears being
always a really really great way to
start off the weekend Monday despite the
fact that this thing has whipped us out
and then as I completely gone into our
take profit so I mean this thing is
going to happen the account is currently
still exactly the same so we literally
got Wicked out on this trade by one pip
like look at this if you come here you
can literally see how I got whipped out
by one pip and then price has been
heading up to the upside if we were to
still be in this trade we'd probably be
up eight nine thousand dollars but it's
okay what I'm gonna be doing is I'm
gonna wait for any higher low on this
trade to enter the trade to the upside
so any higher low I'm going to be
potentially at some buys next is Euro
JPY where we were looking for shorts
earlier this week but we never got any
bearish and rejection structure we
simply don't take the trade the next one
is GBP USD we're gonna wait for the
pullback to this area of Interest round
psychological level in order for us to
take the trade to the downside which is
also going to be retesting the EMA and
on top of that we have your USD which
we're heading up into our zone right
here so GDP Cod wait this out it sucks
it's annoying but we have a beautiful
daily bullish doji rejection Candlestick
now I'm going to see if the next daily
Wick wants to come back and give us a
pool back there in London to see if we
can get it so I'm going to put my alarm
around 3 A.M so I can wake up check it
through my phone one eye and I'm just
gonna like
one night it looks good I take it if now
we'll see if we could catch something in
New York still have plenty of time this
week to make back some profits so we'll
check him back tomorrow in the morning
if not tonight London sessions I'll see
you guys all right so it is 9 40 in the
morning uh I feel a lot better have a
lot more energy it's currently 9 40 in
the morning I usually I've woken up a
little bit later than I usually do that
I was just drained from yesterday with
the students and what I anticipated
yesterday to happen on GBP CAD is
currently happening right now so let me
show you guys so GP cat obviously
yesterday we got Wicked out by literally
nothing like look at that that is not
even a pip and then price had to push to
the upside and then I anticipated
yesterday the only way I will get into
this trade if his price has a pullback
and would you look at that exactly what
I anticipated price is coming back into
this area where I would be looking to
take the trade again so obviously if I
were to not having gotten stopped out I
would still be like this in the trade I
would much rather be in break even area
than a loss but it's okay this shows
that the market is respecting Market
structure so what I'm going to be doing
now here is I'm going to be waiting for
a bullish engulfing for priceland and
golf in order for me to then take this
trade to the upside
um I think it would be if it brings
above that structure level and that EMA
so then that means that price will be
doing something like this so then head
to the upside I do love the fact of how
the daily is now pulling back exactly
how I explained yesterday with the wick
and the four hour I wanted to stay above
this zone right here because it's just
going to keep holding price to head to
the upside next we have Euro JPY so this
is the one that we've been anticipating
for shorts and if you notice we never
broke we never retested so we just never
sold this is the importance of patience
in trading next we have GBP USD which is
already having a rejection but not from
the area of interest that I wanted to
make it to in order for me to sell this
trade I want price to come all the way
back into that area of interest for it
to make sense and then last but not
least we have Euro USD which is still
hasn't made it up to our area of
Interest where we're just you know set
of forgetting letting press do our thing
but our main focus right now is gvp Cap
so sucks that we got Wicked out
yesterday it was something like this and
then uh we're now going to be looking
for an inch or so apparently right now 9
44 in the morning
I'll be updating you guys in the next
hour or two uh so let's see what happens
all right so look at the time that it is
right now 1 45 and we're gonna eat right
now for the first time I literally be
fasting for 12 to 14 hours at a time but
that's good thanks to fasting alone I
think I've lost 14 15 pounds and ate
whatever I want that you could eat
unhealthy you just gotta know when to
eat at the right time so we're about to
eat yeah makes the whole team yeah oh
yeah everybody's fasting it's fasting
fasting they're all like on a 16 hour
fast so you know
around what happened
never would I ever thought it'd be this
guy right here
remember my life
all I think about this stuff for the cat
troll ordered what the hell is this for
litter box [__] we gotta get a better
tray to pick up
I love the rabbits
that's it
oh you look
salmon
real salmon and sweet potato recipe 70
protein 30 vitamins
here's the thing I do for rocket from
Chicago
he likes the ones that make noise
[Music]
so market update I think our last update
was 9 30 in the morning now our next
update is 9 30 at night so let me show
you guys right now where we are we are
exactly in the same exact spot in the
account we've taken absolutely no trade
so the market has been extremely slow
today and I'm gonna be honest I was
catching up on sleep catching up on
messages catching up on Discord like
everything this whole entire day and
luckily for that same reason the market
has been very slow and we might have an
opportunity coming tonight in London
session I'm back in my dark mode like
I'm ready to hit it again because I in
order for me to do this challenge I need
to have 100 laser focus and having all
the pressure of the students here you
know it was a lot so I want you know I
made sure they had a good time made sure
we all had fun you know we got good
podcasts in and most importantly they
all got back home safe so now
everybody's good back to get to the
markets so just check it so GBP CAD
yesterday was the trade that we got
Wicked out right in this area right here
so if you notice we got waked out price
went up and then I expected the pullback
I was saying that earlier this morning I
was going going to enter right around
this area once we had a bullish
engulfing at the Zone then we had a huge
news fluctuation happening but I
obviously wasn't active in the markets
at that time so actively I just kind of
just threw this thing right there on the
chart coincidentally enough it's pretty
much at the same spot I don't like how
the daily time frame has closed I did
explain I was going to expect for that
daily Wick to come back all the way into
the area so that is a good thing I am
going to be strongly debating very very
strongly debating to be entering a trade
in the next 30 minutes to an hour
because we still have plenty of time to
enter the trade before London session I
just don't like the fact how it's been
very choppy around this area right here
but I do like the fact that we are
potentially about to break out of this
zone right here if I don't manage to
enter the trade around where we are now
I'll be looking to enter it at this high
right here once price decides to then
break through this level so it'll be an
Impulse trade during London GB uh Euro
JPY which is our next trade setup which
is the one that we were waiting for
price to break under and then re-test
for us to then go to the downside never
happen we simply never took the trade
our next trade is GBP CAD I mean GBP USD
so this is the first area of interest
that we're looking to then sell uh
obviously I did not want to enter the
trade here I've been waiting for price
to come to this area of interest and it
looks like we are currently headed there
right now and I do see a very clean
potential day trade on GBP USD which is
going to be a retest of this area here
to then make it to this zone right here
this is what I call a high-risk trade
but no risk no Rory okay no risk no
reward so we're going to be waiting for
now is a pull back into this level right
here where I'm going to be waiting for a
little bit of a deeper pullback just a
little bit to make it to the zone right
here so that I can take a quick buy
during London session to this area and
if I manage to do that I'm going to
close very under the air of interest and
then here if we get our rejections then
I will take the longer intraday swing
trade short so this is the power of the
strategy so I'm going to line both of
these things up Euro USD we have the
area of Interest where we've been
expecting for price to come back into it
but I'm going to be on the lookout to
see if it's going to have the rejection
that I need from this area here in order
for us to head to the downside but I do
believe Euro USD will be bullish
throughout the upcoming days but it's
the fifth pair on my watch list and then
last but not least we have
usdchf which is the same thing I'm going
to be waiting for the break and read
this here we've had a major rejection
from the area Avengers which is strongly
what I've been anticipating but we are
holding Above This zone right here so we
have to wait for price to break and
re-test under so everything is looking
very very solid I'm gonna have my focus
on GBP CAD because I think it could be
entering the fastest so I'm going to put
this around this level here and then
next would be GBP USD because Euro JPY
is not happening what we're anticipating
so stay tuned and I've now I'll update
you guys later in London if not tomorrow
in the
it is 9 30 in the morning so exactly
what I explained last night in London
session has happened and I'm going to
explain this quick because I gotta close
this trade but I like to explain it
before I close the trade I always put
you guys before me so let's get into it
so right now in the account we are up
about 13 000 as you guys can tell GBP
kind of the buys that we have taken
yesterday to Perfection you can see
right here how I was expanding yesterday
how I was going to enter at the blow up
and the break of this structure point
and that is exactly what I did so I've
been explaining these lungs Forever on
this trade and you want to know what is
crazy that I've been expecting these
buys all the way since down here we have
taken one buy down here another by here
another by here another by here another
buy here if you guys notice I am just
buying with the trend I'm continuing the
momentum of the markets earlier this
week on Monday right before we got on
the yacht we got Wicked out literally by
nothing look at that by nothing ah but I
mean it is what it is it sucks it's part
of the process you're never going to be
able to know when that's gonna happen
you just have to control show yourself
when it does and stick in the game and
that's exactly what I did I anticipated
how I'm going to be expecting for this
pullback of price into this area so then
we can continue heading to the upside
that is exactly what we are doing right
now so I entered my trade last night as
I explained and then we added a very
small position which is really not
bringing in much profit but we added a
very small position at the higher low
retest of this structure zone right here
so we now continuing heading to the
upside so I'm gonna be debating if I'm
going to close this trade in the next
15-20 minutes I'm just going to close
and hold my profit so I can make back
the losses that I had due to that you
know
well whatever it is what it is and then
yeah Traders are literally happening
exactly as I explained Traders
continuing to the upside and then we're
gonna wait for the next 15 to 20 minute
Candlestick to close so let's see if I
set up forget GBP USD we have officially
made it to the area of Interest the buys
exactly as I explained happened I just
didn't manage to take that trade because
I was paying attention to GBP CAD but if
you guys can tell this is a perfect
example of how the strategy works it is
literally to Perfection look at that I
didn't even move this box and look how
it made it perfectly into that area so
I'm going to be debating now whether I'm
going to be interested in looking to
this trade to sell to the downside and
then last but not least you have your
USD which never rejected our area of
Interest so we're not even going to put
our Focus there but you guys can see how
this is working to perfection
snake
[Music]
I don't know either
[Applause]
fire
we're gonna put this up on the wall
on the white wall so these are all the
cars that I've had big shout out to the
boy Jordan gotcha
that's the 570. this is 570 100. so we
got this here
and this one is
this one is the all right
fire
see what we got over here
Huracan
Lamborghini
I gave mine away
here we go
720 oh fire this actually even looks
like it because of the wing
fire appreciate you brother thank you
I appreciate you so trade update it's
two in the afternoon we ended up closing
the trade exactly where I anticipated it
so as soon as I finished the video up in
the morning I close it literally where I
anticipated it as you guys can see we're
still in that same exact zone right
there it's literally the same spot where
I was in the morning I'm anticipating
now a pullback to enter the trade for
long as again so we realize I'm gonna be
waiting for that retest to then go long
which is going to be a retest of that
zone right there reach it to the EMA to
continue buying the trade as soon as I
close the trade price went up a little
bit more than pulled back and it's right
around the same area
so we finally brought the account back
up we had 13k away from the goal if I
would have not gotten Wicked out by that
trade by a pip I would be at the goal
array so
all right so market update it is
currently midnight so let me show you
guys how the account is looking so we're
currently at 27 000 so this is the
thanks to the trade earlier this morning
that got us up to here if we would have
not gotten Wicked out we would have
probably been at a Target already but
let me show you my effects book so you
guys can see right here how we are
currently of 26 000 these numbers look
absolutely insane but you guys know the
reality behind it twenty seven thousand
dollars you guys can tell right around
here we have a total of 18 trades when
and this trade I mean this week's profit
is only seven thousand dollars even
though we had a big trade but we just
made back the losses that we had and you
can see right here in the p l chart
where we currently are right now and
this is what I'm anticipating for this
week's uh remaining trades so GBP CAD we
could have definitely still been holding
the trade but I personally did not feel
comfortable doing that wanted to get my
profits and just run with it so we're
pretty much in the same area where we
would have closed our take profit if you
wanted to I'm going to still be waiting
for a pullback into this area it's where
I come put my alarm and let's see if we
can get a pullback during London and
then during New York we get the first to
the other side will be the retest of
structure structure structure and then
be the retest of the EMA as well then
GBP USD is what we are anticipating
earlier this week which is the buys to
this level predicted it perfectly
yesterday didn't catch it because we
were focused on GDP CAD so this by
technically we can't leave it on the
history so this trade right now we're
going to be waiting for a break and
retest to themselves to the downside
which is going to look something like
this so both of the pairs that we are
currently interested in look very very
solid to show you guys real time what
time is it it is currently Wednesday uh
11 53. yeah I thought I thought it was
Tuesday
Wednesday wow well we just need thirteen
thousand dollars to be at our take
profit for this week which is 40k I'm
gonna still stay with the same wrists
everything stays absolutely the same
nothing changes I'm just starting it's
midnight so we're gonna hit a quick
workout because I told myself today I
was going to hit a workout I'm going to
go ahead and work out upstairs and then
we will see if we get something in
London if not we'll check back in New
York
all right good morning guys so it is 9
30 in the morning right now and exactly
what I explained last night is happening
to the T so let me show you guys so it
is currently 9 20 in the morning account
is exactly the same and exactly what I
explained last night happened so let me
show you guys so I call myself the
market wizard like literally look what I
sent right here in my free telegram you
guys can see I sent this last night in
London at 2AM I just put the eyes I got
20 000 Traders I've seen it in like
eight hours and then it happened
perfectly I am a wizard
okay so it's just a center forget so
basically exactly what I anticipated
which is the pullback to this area of
Interest so we've made it back to this
area we haven't been able to hold above
the Zone which is good so we avoided the
fact that we could have potentially
gotten in early if you noticed we never
got a bullish engulfing which is always
what I'm waiting for so I avoided that
loss by simply waiting for that so what
I am going to be waiting for now in
order to take this trade is going to be
for something like this and then GBP USD
exactly what I explained yesterday which
was I was looking for the pullback in
this area to then pull back kind of
crazy I haven't even moved this line
that I drew and prices come there
perfectly and what a coincidence I think
from right here we're gonna now start
having the pullback into this area
because of the EMA I just drew this up
super randomly like I literally just
went like this and then it played out
perfectly to that point so we're gonna
see if we can get a pull back into this
area so then we enter the trade store so
everything as of right now is going as
planned
um we have about a couple hours a couple
good hours left in the market of trading
it's currently 9 24 in the morning let's
see if we can manage to enter a trade
either earlier in New York if not London
session tonight so it can play out
throughout London and then tomorrow in
the morning we do it so I'm gonna show
you guys again 9 24 in the morning
Thursday
see what happens like in an hour or two
all right update so it's currently 11 40
in the morning so as of right now the
market is having a reaction as I'm
anticipating but I still can't enter the
trade even though I want to so bad so
let me show you so this is right now GBP
CAD which is the same trade I've been
explaining to you guys we had the
pullback it's waiting for this break and
then the retest I think what we are
doing right now is having this move
right here which is going to be the
brake as of right now we are going to
now have this bullish engulfing
Candlestick close in the next 19 minutes
so I actually just have to wait but I
can't buy under a resistance because if
you see here whenever we're under we're
heading down whenever we're under
heading down whenever we're above we're
heading up so I have to wait for this to
break above retest and then head to the
upside GBP USD which is the trade that I
was anticipating to go down still
rejecting this area right around here
we're going to still be waiting for the
pool back so then head to the downside
so everything stays exactly the same
right now we're gonna go to Neil because
I have my other Richard Mill where I'm
going to be changing the straps and I
might get something new I don't know I'm
kind of tired of the Richard Mill might
trade it for another Richard Mill I
don't know stay tuned we're gonna pull
up literally right now
Alex Gonzalez Alex
so about a year ago I came here I think
it was like about a year and a half ago
I came here and I bought my first
Richard Mill off of Neil and I was a
nurse as [__] man there's no way I'm
about to drop 150 on a bank like my in
bank account like 150 on a watch Yo you
guys want to come to the main office
it'll just be easy
dude this is where you get
this is what he says about me dude
just sudden forget bro look at your
shirt
this way yeah
bro no cop like No Cap No Cap no cop
how many watches have you gotten with
you probably like like five at least ten
five or six oh no that's right a couple
Rolexes as gifts right yeah yeah you've
bought a lot of jewelry that that's why
yeah
I think so I'm not even like like
smiling about it yeah I think so for
sure so today is a special day bro so
today we're gonna we're gonna I don't
give the pendant to anyone unless
they've crushed 100 bro but today
actually like my my account brings it up
like yo he's crossed seven digits and
that's when I'm like [__] I gotta make
you a pendant so you have yeah you know
what we're gonna do today we're gonna
give this to my camera again
and then there's somebody else very
special my team as well we're doing a
guest in the other one to you
okay now you've used that ass no [__] no
give me this [__] I literally text him
like bro you could ask myself like a
week ago I was like yo let's get us a
watch for your birthday yeah he's like
yo don't worry about it yeah yeah [__]
so you guys have you guys gotta just got
to paint meal and then you go we'll be
back
thank you bro
these guys they've done [__] that nobody
else has ever done for me bro so I
appreciate you guys man good for me you
guys I appreciate you just don't just
don't [__] get it Rob you know so
that's that's the only thing
to look at a bus down for himself is
what he told me that's [__] [__] you
oh yeah yeah you're not getting one for
yourself anymore yeah I think I'll do
something
just take care of the gang that's
awesome
um real one right here 100 this is super
hard bro you actually did that that's a
coffee table yeah with the real movement
and it keeps the time Mr Sebastian
look I have green rubber it's designed
to be rich again look at this soup but I
don't know if it'll fit it's a medium I
could try I think it'll fit you bro you
think so
[Music]
um you had an rm11
you've had a norm 30. yeah I think you
should do a factory bubble bro this is
an fxl experience yeah that's meteorite
oh this is that's faster this is classic
how much is this see Sean you know how
much the sorrow is
all Factory full set 2021 wow that's
crazy this is also a good daily bro for
you I think solid gold sub I would only
get going to this rose gold and got it
yeah I feel like oh yellow gold I'm
already Cuban I look like a [__] yeah
there's nothing really in here for you
then oh not a flip a coin for that 10K
you and Sean can do it for for 5K
all right so we're flipping for four
grand
the 4K flip so either it's 14k or 10K
okay but best two out of three or one
bro you can decide I'll let you decide
the Fate it's a very fair system here we
got heads
this is this is definitely heavier on
one side all right all right
good choice
um I get to flip it though you get to
flip it I get the flipping you get to
call it okay that's that's the rules all
right so Tails best 23. all right let's
go oh [__] yeah he's worth it okay
that's the first one
you could steal your fate right now with
the next flip but I hope it lands head
so there's some drama you know I have a
little bit of drama
heads times two that's twice oh
[__] dude this is such a [__] up coin
flip because I forgot we don't win
anything no there's a rule yeah
all right this is it this is it this is
the big moment this could be uh This is
Gonna Change the rest of your day bro
this is like either like maybe Komodo
launch or or maybe like you have to go
like to Kyoto or some [__] you know what
I'm saying
let's go so I don't ever have coins
around me bro honestly I own him I owe
him that one because of all the flips
that we did exactly and I always get fun
at the crib yeah and we played poker at
my house on my [__] and I always lose
everybody's making money
is this
yeah
yeah he never misses
so market update just got back home
probably like an hour ago we spent all
day celebrating you know uh Sebastian's
birthday we got him the Rolex got myself
the new Rolex got myself the Richard
another Richard I think this is like my
fifth Richard I don't know
it's like I don't know just turns into
watches at this time but Mark it up
there because I think we might get our
last trade where we're gonna be able to
then have our goal for the end of the
week which is 40k so let me show you
guys so it's GBP USD but beforehand let
me show you guys the account that it is
currently in the exact same point as of
right now 11 o'clock at night and then
you guys can see that GBP USD I am
anticipating for price to break the
serial retest so we already had a very
fast retest I do believe we can maybe
come back a little bit deeper before
heading to the downside or what I'm
going to be waiting for is I'm going to
be waiting for a break of this area
right here like I need prices just break
the under this area retest it and then
I'll be looking for some quick cells and
and then GBP CAD never gave us our entry
signal GBP CAD did not respect the area
where we were looking to buy the trade
we never retest and have it to the
upside so we simply never took the trade
but we are back at this area once again
where I got Wicked out earlier this week
right here and then we entered this
trade right here but we're back at the
same area where we got waked out earlier
this week which is crazy and if we get
another entry signal at this area I
would definitely be taking the same
exact trade I took here the same exact
trade I took here and the same exact
trade I took here so the three buys at
the same Zone every single time we come
here we reject up every single time here
we reject up we reject up so I'm simply
just gonna do the same thing again it's
very simple so I'm going to be waiting
for now any type of rejection
confirmation around this area which is
gonna happen very very soon so it looks
like we're gonna line up for some trades
tonight in London so stay tuned for
tomorrow uh in the morning update let's
go all right what is up guys so exactly
what I explain last night has happened
to Perfection this is a beautiful trade
and it shows you we're just doing the
same thing over and over again and how
the satin forget strategy Works to
Perfection look at this so you guys can
see right now this is where we are on
the account we are of twenty thousand
dollars on GDP card exactly what I
explained yesterday if price comes back
into this area gives me my energy signal
I'm gonna do it again we got it here one
time we caught it here two times three
times and now once again this is a
beautiful indication you guys cannot
tell me this is the most beautiful
inverted Head and Shoulders you have
seen at an area of Interest with a
beautiful entry signal like it does not
get any cleaner than that does not get
any cleaner than that and on top of that
London Station and on top of that London
session come on man I am telling you
guys the set and forget strategy is the
most precise as it gets bro you guys see
me doing this time and time and time
again and I've only taken two trades
this week look at the results that I
have with only two trades we are
focusing on quality not quantity all
right so I was hyped let me uh come back
down so I'm gonna give it another 15-20
minutes I'm gonna see if I close the
trade or not I'm just very hyped because
we met our goal for the week and this is
what I like about setting yourself to my
chat and just reaching these goals like
all these little small wins
um so that feels good now I'm gonna wait
to see if we close in the next 15
minutes I believe and let's see how we
if we're gonna keep holding or we just
close it right there and where we end up
in the account and just like that boys
we have officially closed the trade we
even got rocket watching us over here so
let me show you guys exactly where we
close the trade this is crazy so we beat
our goal by six thousand dollars for the
week you guys can see that we close off
the week at 46 000 in profit if I show
you guys here the my effects book as
well you guys can see that this is what
we are up on the account it is the same
exact amount from the same exact deposit
amount you can see the p l chart and you
can see this week's profits along with
this week's gains percentage-wise you
can see the Pips you can see everything
you can see are the total trades that
we've taken 20 trades in a row how many
trades I have one that are Longs how
many trades I have one that are shorts
like this shows you guys and this shows
you guys the stats of this Challenge and
it shows you guys that I am literally
documenting this whole entire thing I am
showing you guys how this is possible
I've only taken two trades this week
all of my Center forget students have
caught in this everybody on Instagram
this trade I put on my Instagram go look
at my Instagram highlights from the 100
to the mail everything is documented
like
we are closer than you can imagine to
achieving this challenge stay tuned boys
so let's do a recap of how the week
started so we obviously first started
the week with Sunday Swings with the
students where we broke down the top
three top four pairs for the week and
then you guys can see how we had the
students here at the house and then we
did something Swings with the students
in my house so it was a super cool
experience and then the goal was for me
to catch a profitable trade so we would
get on the yaw and kind of do like cool
content like oh create a lifestyle like
show the profits and stuff but yeah GDP
Cat decided to work us out it happens so
we started off the week with a loss on
Monday morning right before we got in
the yacht so that right there is a
perfect lesson that shows there is no
way to avoid it in the market so it's
literally impossible the Market's gonna
do it you just have to get used to it
that's what you have to use risk
management so first start off Monday
with the loss but then later throughout
the week you can see how I enter again
GP cab at another buy pretty much at the
same Zone but with the same entry signal
and the same entry strategy we made
enough profit to bring our account back
up because we were down to thirteen
thousand dollars and then on Thursday
night right before Friday I explained to
you guys the perfect GP card that was
going to happen once again which is the
same exact trade that we got Wicked out
at the beginning of the week on Monday
and then we ended up taking the same
exact trade same exact Zone the same
stop loss but then that trade made us to
get to our account to where it is now
it's a forty six thousand dollars so it
was a very simple week and you guys can
see how we did the same exact trade
three times on the same pair on the same
area of interest is keeping it super
simple and you guys can see how hundreds
of my students are using my certificate
strategy to generate anywhere from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week as a beginner trade using
my set and forget strategy in three
months or less if you guys want to know
more about what seven forget is just
click the link in the description below
I have a video for you guys that
explains it perfectly you guys are
seeing how I'm having these winning
streaks week after week and I'm
predicting these trades day after day
trade after trade live you understand
the before and after so yeah guys want
to know more about my set and forget and
more than just this video click the link
in the description below I have an
invitation for you which is going to
make so much sense appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end make sure to tune in next week
because we're going to be trying taking
the Forty thousand dollar profits that
we have now all the way to eighty
thousand dollars I can already feel like
I'm gonna complete this challenge so
thank you guys for watching all the way
to the end I'll see you guys in the next
video